{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0000", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Bright, modern room with panoramic window in Maspeth for 8 nights?", "answer": "$ 42450.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0001", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Quiet and spacious room for 2 in Maspeth for 4 nights?", "answer": "$ 3848.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0002", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Cozy Vintage Artist Flat(Williamsburg/Bushwick) in Bedford-Stuyvesant for 14 nights?", "answer": "$ 840.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0003", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Beautiful loft in DUMBO Brooklyn in Vinegar Hill for 7 nights?", "answer": "$ 3661.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0004", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Ditmas Park Beauty in Flatbush for 2 nights?", "answer": "$ 3498.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0005", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Peaceful, cozy studio in Chinatown in Chinatown for 9 nights?", "answer": "$ 13820.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0006", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Home away from home in Canarsie for 2 nights?", "answer": "$ 488.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0007", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at An East Williamsburg Delight in Bedford-Stuyvesant for 12 nights?", "answer": "$ 6552.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0008", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Queen Sized Bdrm in Historic Harlem (Townhouse) in Harlem for 20 nights?", "answer": "$ 8020.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0009", "question": "What is the total price at least if you want to stay at Cozy and Cute 1 bdrm in perfect Midtown location in Hell's Kitchen for 8 nights?", "answer": "$ 12360.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0010", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Rosedale?", "answer": "171"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0011", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Flatlands?", "answer": "217"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0012", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Brighton Beach?", "answer": "168"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0013", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Whitestone?", "answer": "26"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0014", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Jamaica Estates?", "answer": "50"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0015", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Windsor Terrace?", "answer": "331"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0016", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Port Richmond?", "answer": "25"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0017", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Bronxdale?", "answer": "48"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0018", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Roosevelt Island?", "answer": "159"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0019", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Van Nest?", "answer": "26"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0020", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Boerum Hill?", "answer": "$ 627.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0021", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Schuylerville?", "answer": "$ 659.4"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0022", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Maspeth?", "answer": "$ 597.0"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0023", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Sheepshead Bay?", "answer": "$ 624.9"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0024", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Grant City?", "answer": "$ 558.2"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0025", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in East Morrisania?", "answer": "$ 764.7"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0026", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Howland Hook?", "answer": "$ 657.3"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0027", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Glen Oaks?", "answer": "$ 550.5"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0028", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Queens Village?", "answer": "$ 661.9"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0029", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Stuyvesant Town?", "answer": "$ 680.9"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0030", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from Spacious 1 BR in Midtown East in Midtown?", "answer": "3.27"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0031", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from 10 mins/Airports JFK/LGA/Hosp/malls bus/train#4 in Richmond Hill?", "answer": "3.39"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0032", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from Williamsburg Home with a View in Williamsburg?", "answer": "3.28"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0033", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from Spacious Midtown East 2 Bedroom in Midtown?", "answer": "3.27"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0034", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from Slick Prime Lower East East ~BRAND NEW 1br Apt~ in Lower East Side?", "answer": "3.27"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0035", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from Heart of Park Slope in Park Slope?", "answer": "3.26"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0036", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from Charming Mini Loft/ Lower East Side in Lower East Side?", "answer": "3.27"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0037", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from 3 Bedrooms, 1000 Pvt Sq ft in Historic Brownstone. in Harlem?", "answer": "3.26"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0038", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from NEWLY RENOVATED,  studio in Park Slope in Park Slope?", "answer": "3.26"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0039", "question": "What is the average review rates within 5 miles from Wonderful apartment with view & Rooftop!!!! in Astoria?", "answer": "3.28"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0040", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in West Brighton have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.31"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0041", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Fordham have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.31"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0042", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Ditmars Steinway have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.3"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0043", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Co-op City have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.2"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0044", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in SoHo have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.34"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0045", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Wakefield have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.4"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0046", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in East Elmhurst have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.33"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0047", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Wakefield have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.4"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0048", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Howland Hook have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.17"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0049", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Stuyvesant Town have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.33"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0050", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Eastchester?", "answer": "$961"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0051", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Throgs Neck?", "answer": "$984"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0052", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Kingsbridge?", "answer": "$978"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0053", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Emerson Hill?", "answer": "$317"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0054", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Williamsbridge?", "answer": "$990"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0055", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Edgemere?", "answer": "$964"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0056", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Morningside Heights?", "answer": "$997"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0057", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Howard Beach?", "answer": "$968"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0058", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Kew Gardens?", "answer": "$931"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0059", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive entire home/apt in Fort Wadsworth?", "answer": "$1,024"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0060", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Little Italy that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "119"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0061", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Springfield Gardens that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "115"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0062", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Eltingville that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0063", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Belmont that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "21"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0064", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Concord that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "28"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0065", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Douglaston that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0066", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Prospect-Lefferts Gardens that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "550"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0067", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Randall Manor that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "25"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0068", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Financial District that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "714"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0069", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Norwood that have a review rate higher than 4?", "answer": "32"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0070", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in College Point?", "answer": "Doris’s Fresh House"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0071", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in SoHo?", "answer": "Greenwich village 1 bedroom - spacious!"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0072", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Eltingville?", "answer": "“No Place Like Home”\n1st Floor Suburban Apt."}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0073", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Holliswood?", "answer": "ROOM EN NEW YORK, MANHATTAN"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0074", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Concourse?", "answer": "One Bedroom Apartment  in TownHouse"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0075", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Silver Lake?", "answer": "New Apartment, Close to Ferry"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0076", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Bull's Head?", "answer": "Newly Renovated Guest Room with Private Bath"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0077", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Westerleigh?", "answer": "Eclectic Private New Apartment  Westerleigh, S.I."}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0078", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in NoHo?", "answer": "Clean and Stylish Noho Loft w/ Comfy King Bed"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0079", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Clifton?", "answer": "Cozy Bedroom & Private Bath/Full use of Amenities"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0080", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in College Point?", "answer": "Beautiful and Clean Private Bedroom with Bathroom"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0081", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in St. George?", "answer": "@FERRY, Private Cozy Room, Renovated&Stylish."}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0082", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in Flatiron District?", "answer": "Sonder Flatiron | Spacious King Room+"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0083", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in Co-op City?", "answer": "A unique apartment,  clean, quiet, and peaceful !"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0084", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in Howard Beach?", "answer": "PRIVATE, NEWLY RENOVATED BEDROOM, 10 MINS FROM JFK"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0085", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in Tribeca?", "answer": "Classic, yet Unconventional Tribeca NYC Extra Room"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0086", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in Castleton Corners?", "answer": "2 Bedrooms across from a Beautiful Park"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0087", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in Edenwald?", "answer": "Luxury Affordable comfort in the Bronx-Suite 3!"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0088", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in Dongan Hills?", "answer": "comfortable & cozy qns size bed Feel it yourself"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0089", "question": "Can you recommend me a private room with the highest review rate that can host at least 2 people in Nolita?", "answer": "Great Room in Charming Nolita Apartment"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0090", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -74.06269614778004 longitude and 40.5813729578663 latitude?", "answer": "Premium Spot for female. Close to subway & Park"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0091", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -73.79998226317166 longitude and 40.581286157201006 latitude?", "answer": "Quiet & Elegant, 30 mins to midtown Manhattan!"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0092", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -73.70247078883878 longitude and 40.58720602526452 latitude?", "answer": "Home Away From Home"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0093", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -73.83109495286112 longitude and 40.835727665445795 latitude?", "answer": "Brand New Renovated Shared Room In  Manhattan"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0094", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -74.0426082801347 longitude and 40.689902908795524 latitude?", "answer": "Comfortable Futon Couch in Brooklyn"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0095", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -73.72509182668071 longitude and 40.79002903608048 latitude?", "answer": "Partitioned (shared) Cozy Studio in Pelham Bay"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0096", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -73.81552366025818 longitude and 40.89104376829842 latitude?", "answer": "Partitioned (shared) Cozy Studio in Pelham Bay"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0097", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -74.09292883460675 longitude and 40.72347282747828 latitude?", "answer": "Living room available! Modern apartment in midtown"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0098", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -73.91523625637042 longitude and 40.867183473498066 latitude?", "answer": "Brand New Renovated Shared Room In  Manhattan"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0099", "question": "Can you recommend a shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles from -73.89471040722765 longitude and 40.60167851935561 latitude?", "answer": "Comfortable Futon Couch in Brooklyn"}
